{
    "subject": "resource/Charlie_Chan_Carries_On_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/studio",
    "object": "resource/Fox_Film",
    "human_readable": "The film Charlie Chan Carries On was produced by Fox Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881526827812195,
            "question": "Is 'Charlie Chan Carries On' a film produced by Fox Film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939465343952179,
            "question": "Who produced the film 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8215650320053101,
            "question": "What is the name of the film production company that made 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7913830876350403,
            "question": "Which studio was responsible for producing 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7538177371025085,
            "question": "Who starred in 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7475109100341797,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Fox Film."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.581179141998291,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'Charlie Chan Carries On' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5801190733909607,
            "question": "Is 'Charlie Chan Carries On' a television show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5226501822471619,
            "question": "What type of media is 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37033143639564514,
            "question": "What film title includes the phrase 'Carries On'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Charlie Chan Carries On was produced by Fox Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3535_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of media is 'Charlie Chan Carries On'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3535_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Charlie Chan Carries On' a television show?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3535_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre might the film 'Charlie Chan Carries On' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3535_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3535_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the production company of the film \"Charlie Chan Carries On,\" stating under \"Production\" that it was distributed by \"Fox Film Corporation.\" This supports the statement that the film was produced by Fox Film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}